Bartosz Glinka

Junior Web Developer

Profile

I have been responsible for customer contact for over a five years with plenty of sales experience. I'm characterized by a proactvie approach to co-creating a bussiness and the ability to effectively diagnose customer requirement

Technologies

 HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, REACT, REDUX, TDD, NODE.JS, WEBSOCKET, EXPRESS, MONGODB, MONGOOSE

Lanuages

• Polish : Native

• English - Upper-Intermediate

Contact Information

Address: Warsaw Phone: 513-449-495

Email: bartosz.glinka@hotmail.com GitHub: github.com/BartoszGlinka LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/bartosz-

glinka

Career History

CUSTOMER CONTACT REPRESENTATIVE

Printex Sp. z o.o. Sp. k | October 2019 - present

CO-OWNER OF STRATEGY AND DEVELOPMENT

Spółdzielnia Socjalna 4Smart | January 2017 -September 2019

EXECUTIVE BOARD MEMBER

Stowarzyszenie Brzask | April 2015 - September 2019

Academic Background

WARSAW UNIVERSITY OF LIFE SCIENCES

M.A. Management Graduated June 2018

 With specialization: Management and marketing in the enterprise

CARDINAL STEFAN WYSZYŃSKI UNIVERSITY IN WARSAW

B.A. Economy Graduated June 2015

 With specialization: Analysis of the financial and economic market

Courses

CODEMY S.A.

Web Developer Plus March 2019 - November 2020

- Projects:
 - Template CRM HTML/CSS
 - Online Shop JS, JIRA, GIT